Annabel: Hello. I’m Annabel.
Peter: And I’m Peter.
Expert: Hi there, Annabel and Peter.
What’s your problem?
Annabel: We’ve got a son, Jamie, and he’s twenty-five.
He’s a chef.
Peter: But he still lives with us because he says
it’s too expensive to rent a flat and he doesn’t earn enough money.
Annabel: He gives us some money every month for bills – not much, but a bit – and,
you know, it’s nice to have him at home, but we think he needs to be more independent.
Peter: Yes, absolutely.
Annabel: But last week he told us that
he’s planning a two-week holiday to Mexico with his friends.
I mean, it’s true that he works full-time and we know he needs a break, but we really think…
Peter: Yes, we don’t think he should go on an expensive holiday when
he doesn’t give us much money.
We think he should save his money so that he can get his own place to live.
Should we tell him that he can’t go to Mexico?